Forcing me to back down step by step
The Su family
Wants me to go back
Come back first
Apologize to both Cheng Ze and Yu
And delete those things online
There's still room to turn things around
They want you to apologize
Yeah
Are you going to
No
But I'll go back
They won't just make me apologize today
There's something else
A supplementary agreement
That's exactly what happened in my past life
Being pushed out to take the fall
How do you know
Because I don't want to fall for
The same trick twice
Let's go I am your legal husband
When you go back to the Su family
Me tagging along won't be out of place
Mr Fu gets into character very fast
Mrs Fu adapted just as fast last night
Heh
Then let's go
Sister
Why did you bring Mr Fu along
He is my husband
Do you have to remind everyone every time you speak